

585 Purdue Mall ME3171, West Lafayette, IN 47907

🛮 (415)203-8543 | 🗷 hyung-gun | 🎓 engineering.purdue.edu/people/hyung.gun.chi.1 | 🗖 stnoah1 | 🛅 hyung-gun | 🎓 Hyung-gun Chi

Research Interests

My research interests lie in the fields of Computer Vision and Machine Learning. More specifically, I am interested in the Representation Learning for human action, 3D Computer Vision, and their applications in VR / AR devices and Autonomous Vehicles.

Education

Purdue UniversityWest Lafayette, IN, USA

PHD IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

Dec. 2023 (Expected)

Dec. 2022

Feb 2017

• Thesis: Learning Representation for Understanding Human Action

• Advisor: Professor Karthik Ramani

Purdue University West Lafayette, IN, USA

MS IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING

· Advisor: Professor Karthik Ramani

Yonsei University Seoul, South Korea

BS IN MECHANICAL ENGINEERING

• Advisor: Professor Soo-Hong Lee

Publications and Patents

Conference Proceedings

- [C7] H. Chi, K. Lee, N. Agarwal, K. Ramani, and C. Choi. AdamsFormer for Spatial Action Localization in the Future, *Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR)*, 2023. Submitted.
- [C6] H. Chi, S. Chi, Q. Huang, and K. Ramani. Skeleton-ODE: Learning Representation by Predicting the Future for Online Skeleton-based Action Recognition, Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2023. Submitted.
- [C5] Y. Xu, A. Bazarjani, H. Chi, C. Choi, and Y. Fu. Uncovering the Missing Pattern: Unified Framework Towards Trajectory Imputation and Prediction, *Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR)*, 2023. Submitted.
- [C4] H. Chi, S. Chi, S. Chan, and K. Ramani. Pose Relation Transformer: Refine Occlusions for Human Pose Estimation, *IEEE International Conference on Robotics and Automation (ICRA)*, 2023. Submitted.
- [C3] H. Chi, M. Ha, S. Chi, S. Lee, Q. Huang, and K. Ramani. InfoGCN: Representation Learning for Human Skeleton-based Action Recognition, In proceedings of *Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR)*, 2022.
- [C2] H. Chi, S. Kim, X. Hu, Q. Huang, and K. Ramani. A Large-scale Mechanical Components Benchmark for Deep Neural Networks. In proceedings of the 16th European Conference on Computer Vision (ECCV), 2020.
- [C1] S. Kim, H. Chi, and K. Ramani. First-Person View Hand Segmentation of Multi-Modal Hand Activity Video Dataset. In proceedings of the 31st British Machine Vision Conference (BMVC), 2020.

Journal Papers

- [J3] S. Kim, H. Chi and K. Ramani. Object synthesis by learning part geometry with surface and volumetric representations. In Computer-Aided Design (2021): 102932.
- [J2] S. Kim, N. Winovich, H. Chi, G. Lin, and K. Ramani. Latent transformations neural network for object view synthesis. In *The Visual Computer* (2019): 1-15.
- [J1] H. T. Hwang, H. Chi, N. K. Kang, H. B. Kong and Soo-Hong Lee. An Evaluation Methodology for 3D Deep Neural Network using Visualization in 3D Data Classification. In *Journal of Mechanical Science and Technology (JMST)* 33, no. 3 (2019): 1333-1339.

Preprinted papers

• S. Kim, J. Bae, **H. Chi**, S. Hong, B.S. Koh, and K. Ramani. Egocentric View Hand Action Recognition by Leveraging Hand Surface and Hand Grasp Type. *arXiv preprint arXiv:2109.03783*, 2021.

Patents

RESEARCH INTERN

- [P2] K. Ramani, S. Kim, and H. Chi. Pixel-wise Hand Segmentation of Multi-modal Hand Activity Video Dataset. U.S. Patent Application No. 17/109,193.
- [P1] H. Chi. Computer Input Automation System. KR Patent No. 10-1745330, issued 2017.

Work Experience

Honda Research Institute

San Jose, CA, USA

Jan. 2023 - Apr. 2023

• Conducted human pose prediction research for autonomous vehicles.

Honda Research Institute San Jose, CA, USA

May. 2022 - Aug. 2022 RESEARCH INTERN

- Conducted research on future action forcasting task for autonomous vehicles.
- Developed a transformer-based alorithm for the task.

NEIL LAB Corporation Seoul, South Korea Sep. 2016 - Dec. 2017

SOFTWARE ENGINEER & CEO

- Founded and manage a start-up company as a CEO and senior software engineer.
- · Developed an office automation system specifically for automating office tasks such as sending an e-mail or issuing receipts.

• Designed a back-end system and database for customer web-service which automatically collects and integrate financial and personal data. (Relevant patent: [P1])

Skills

Research and Development Stacks Other Tools and Skills

Major Languages Python, C/C++ **Text Editors** Neovim & Vim

Machine Learning PyTorch, TensorFlow, Keras Other Langauges Shell Scripts(bszh, zsh), Matlab(Octave), R Web Frameworks Django, Flask, Node.js **Operating Systems** macOS, Linux Debian/Ubuntu, Windows

Computer Vision OpenCV, OpenGL IDE VSCode, Eclipse, IDEA Web Languages Nginx, React, HTML5, PHP, JavaScript, CSS **Softwares** SolidWorks, Catia, AutoCAD

Database MySQL, PostgreSQL, SQLite, MongoDB VCS Git

Academic Activities

Reviewer

• The IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition (CVPR) 2023

- The British Machine Vision Conference (BMVC) 2020, 2021, 2022
- · Journal of Visual Communication and Image Representation (JVCI)
- · Journal of Computing and Information Science in Engineering (JCISE)

Invited Talks_

Hongik University Seoul, South Korea

Dec. 2022

Guest Lecturer: Learning Representation for Human Action Recognition

References_

Karthik Ramani Professor, Purdue University ramani@purdue.edu **Soo-Hong Lee** Professor, Yonsei University shlee@yonsei.ac.kr